Guide to the University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1845-present UA.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1924-March 1925 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1926; 6.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1925; 7.
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 15, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 23, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 9 and June 18, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1925; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 18, 1925; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 15, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 14, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 29, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 13 and 27, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1925; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 27, 1925; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 29-November 1925 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 29, 1925; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 30, 1925; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 24, 1925; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1925-February 1926 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 8, 1925; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 29, 1925; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 8, 1926; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-June 1926 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 9, 1926; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 6, 1926; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1926; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1926; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, July-October 12, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 8, 1926; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 21, 1926; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 12, 1926; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 14-December 7, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1926; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 19, 1926; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 30, 1926; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 7, 1926; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 14, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 27, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-June 1927 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1927; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 20, 1927; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1927; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1927 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1927; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 18, 1927; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1927 and March 1928 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1927; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1928; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 13, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, April-October, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 16, 1928; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1928; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1928; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 30, 1928; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1928-April 1929 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1928; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1929; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 23, 1929; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, May-June, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 1, 1929; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1929; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 25, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October-December, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1929; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 10, 1929; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-November, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1930; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 25, 1930; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1930; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 11, 1930; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, October 14, 1924-September 11, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October-December 1930 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1930; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1930; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1930; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 13, 1931; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1931; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 4, 1931; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1931; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 30, 1931; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1931; 6.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1931; 7.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 10, 1931; 8.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 10, 1931; 9.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 8, 1931; 10.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-April, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1932; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 5, 1932; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1932-March 1933 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1932; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 18, 1932; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 25, 1932; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1932; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 14, 1933; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 17, 1933; 6.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 13 and October 10, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 13, 1933; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 10, 1933; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 17, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1933; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 29, 1933; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 8, 1934; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 13, 1934; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1934; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1934; 6.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 23, 1934; 7.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1934; 8.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 7, 1934; 9.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1934; 10.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March 1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1935; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 14, 1935; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, April-November 1935 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 3, 1935; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 22, 1935; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1935; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1935; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 13, 1935; 5.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1935 - March 1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 10, 1935; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1936; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 24, 1936; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 8, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1936 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1936; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1936; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, October 14, 1930-June 1936 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 28, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 28, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Treasurer and Auditor Annual Reports, June 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 8, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 8, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Condensed Budget Report, December 1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 18, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 18, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 19, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 19, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 9, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 31, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 8, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 30, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, September 30, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 27, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 14, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 14, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 9, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 9, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 21, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, April 21, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 7, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, September 7, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 7, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 7, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 20, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 20, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 13, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 15, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, September 15, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 17, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 17, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Treasurer and Auditor Annual Reports, June 1939 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 19, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 19, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 6, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 11, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 10, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 30, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 17, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 17, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 11, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 17, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 6, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 6, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- University of Pittsburgh, General Budget Report, October and November 1941 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- University of Pittsburgh, Treasurer and Auditor Annual Reports, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 9, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 9, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 9, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 22, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, April 22, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 9, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 29, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 29, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 30, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 25, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 25, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 8, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 30, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, April 30, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 28, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, General Budget 1943-44, June 28, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 20, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 29, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 31, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 31, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Copy of Annual Meeting Minutes Filed in Fiscal Year 1944, July 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 16, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 16, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 16, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 16, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 2, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, May 2, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 12, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 9, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of Board of Trustees, December 11, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 11, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 12, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 6)